{
    "subject": "resource/The_Adventures_of_Rocky_and_Bullwinkle",
    "predicate": "ontology/narrator",
    "object": "resource/Keith_Scott_(voice_actor)",
    "human_readable": "The narrator of The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle is Keith Scott.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9592484831809998,
            "question": "Who narrates the Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8680291771888733,
            "question": "What is the name of the narrator for the cartoon show featuring Rocky and Bullwinkle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6862510442733765,
            "question": "Name a popular cartoon series narrated by Keith Scott."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6548548340797424,
            "question": "Is Keith Scott known for narrating cartoons?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5380483865737915,
            "question": "Are there any famous catchphrases associated with The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5327329635620117,
            "question": "Besides narrating, what other roles has Keith Scott played in the entertainment industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5123664736747742,
            "question": "Who are the main characters in The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4410468637943268,
            "question": "What type of humor is typically found in The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.37165266275405884,
            "question": "What makes The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle unique?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20806878805160522,
            "question": "What time period does The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle typically take place in?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The narrator of The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle is Keith Scott.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6272_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What makes The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle unique?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6272_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of humor is typically found in The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6272_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are the main characters in The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6272_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6272_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6272_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6272_116.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6272_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6272_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6272_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6272_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6272_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6272_85.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6272_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can provide an answer in the form of a structured JSON format.\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe information from the documents supports the triple that the narrator of The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle is indeed Keith Scott. This is confirmed in multiple documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6272/re-ranker-msmarco/22.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6272/re-ranker-msmarco/97.txt, and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6272/re-ranker-msmarco/29.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\"output\": \"yes\"}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that \"Bullwinkle (voiced by Keith Scott, who also voices the Narrator) and Rocky (voiced by June Foray, the original voice of Rocky)\" which supports the statement that Keith Scott is the narrator of The Adventures of Rocky and Bullwinkle."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}